Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Charges, Claims, and Arbitrations
  - Denmark Cheese Association, re: Jack Haskwll and Allyn Edwards, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Diamond, Selma v. Firestone and Associates, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Disciplinary Hearings: Baker, Paul, Dukas, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Dodge, Marshall: Payment Issue, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Domar Productions: Muppets Appearance on "That's Life", 1969 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Domino Productions: "The Golddiggers", 1972 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Don Buchwald and Associates v. Elvira Roussel, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Douglas, Alan v. NBC, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Dukas, James: In the Matter Of, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Dworkin, Stan: "Saturday Morning Live", 1983 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Ed Sullivan Productions: Doodletown Pipers, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Eckhert, Julie: Termination from ABC (Newscaster), 1981 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Engel, George: "Voices in the Headlines", 1977 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Farrantino, James: Pension and Welfare Funds Payments, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Faso, Laurie: "Marlo and the Magic Movie Machine", 1977-1980 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Felscher, Howard: Barry Farber Interview Show, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Franklin, Joe: Payments, 1972-1976 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Funt, Allen: "Candid Camera", 1967 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Funt, Allen: Extras for "Only Human", 1981 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - General, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - General, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - General, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - General Artists Corporation: "Away We Go", 1967 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Generich, William: ABC Staff Announcers Grievances, 1974-1976 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Gleason, Jackie: "American Scene Magazine", 1977-1981 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Gleason, Jackie: Foreign Use of "The Jackie Gleason Show", 1970 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Gleason, Jackie: "The Jackie Gleason Show" Residuals, 1980-1983 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Gibson, Virginia: "3-2-1 Contact", 1980 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Granger, Michael: "Yulya", 1979 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Gribbin, Robert: "One Life to Live", 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - H.A. Artists and Associates Inc. v. Richard van Vleet, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - Harrington, James: Stand-By Overtime, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Hawkins, Michael: "Love is a Many Splendored Thing", 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - HBO: "Great American Ghost Tour", 1982 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - HBO: "The Passion of Dracula", 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Hehn Joseph P.: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Heitz, Gail: Erroneous Commission Payment, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - Henson Associates: "The Muppet Show", 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - Holiday, Bob: Transferred Membership, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - Hoving, Thomas: ABC Pension and Welfare, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Howard, Shirley: Disability Compensation, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Huntley, Chester: Horizons Communication Corporation, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - Hunter, Jeff v. Narizzano, Dino, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - Ingram, Daniel: Opening and Closing Announcements for WABC, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - Institute for the Development of Educational Activities: "Green, Green: Song Use, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - J. Walter Thompson Comany: Overpayment, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - Jane L. Limited: "We'll Be Right Back", 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - Jordan, Bob v. WOR-TV and AFTRA NY-Local: EEOC Complaint, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - Jordan, Bob v. WOR-TV and AFTRA NY-Local: EEOC Complaint, 1977-1980 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - Kay, Georgie: "Here Come the Stars", 1969 (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - KCET: N.E.T. Contract Overtime Payment, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 71)
  - Kennedy, Kevin: Sick Leave, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 72)
  - Kerr, James: "Jim Kerr Show", 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 73)
  - Kiamos, Eleni: Unemployment Insurance Claim, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - King, Bob: "Clay Cole Show", 1967 (Box 46, Folder 75)
  - King-Hitzig Productions: "Children of Adam", 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 76)
  - Knauth, Carlos v. Bartell Broadcasters of New York, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 77)
  - Knight, Terry: Cameo-Parkway Records, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 78)
  - KPNX v. Joyce Michell et al, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 79)
  - L.F. Music Inc.: Jerome L. Jackson, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Landay, Jerry: Severance Pay, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Lanza, Jose: "Hit del Momento", 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Leaverton Associates LTD: David Bailey, 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Leaverton Associates LTD v. Paul Stevens, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Letterman, David: Show, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Levine, BennettL AFTRA Membership Fees, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Abby: CLIO Awards Festival, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lionel Larner LTD v. William Money, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Local 1212 IBEW v. WPIX, 1981-1984 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - M.F. Records: "The Tonight Show", 1974 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - M.F. Records: "The Tonight Show", 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - M.F. Records: "The Tonight Show", 1976-1979 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Machson v. AFTRA, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Macrae, Sheila: ABC Records, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Marshall, Paul: "The Down Five", 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Marsteller v. Stiller and Meara, 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Martin, David: ABC Pension and Welfare Claim, 1975-1982 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Marvin Josephson Associates v. Phyllis George, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Marvin Josephson Associates v. Rollin, Betty, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Mary Murphy Agency v. Chris Hubbell, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Mel Baily Productions: Children's Festival NBC, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Meunier, Claudine: Application Fees, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - McDonald, Thomas: Pension and Welfare Fees, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: 1-9, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: A, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: ABC, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Another World", 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: B, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: C, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: D, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: E-F, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: G, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Great Space Coaster", 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Guiding Light", 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: H, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: I-K, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: L, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: M, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: N-O, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "One Life to Live", 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: P-R, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: S, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Saturday Night Live", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Saturday Night Live", Jan 1983-Jul 1983 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: "Saturday Night Live", Aug 1983-May 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: T, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: Tony Awards, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members: U-Z, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Monies Collected for Members: Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Morgan, Henry: "Tonight Show", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Morgan, Monty: "Girl Talk", 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Mutual Broadcasting System: Tony Marvin, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Mutual Broadcasting System: News Cut-Ins, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Nader, Michael: Benton and Bowles Termination, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - National Education Television: "Peggy Lee Special" Replay Fees, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Navarro, Frank: Inter-Americas Advertising, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - NBC: "Another World" Assorted Claims, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - NBC: Peter Hackes, Robert Goralski, Carl Stern, John Palmer, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - NBC: "Howdy Doody", 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - NBC: "The Jerry Lewis Show", 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - NBC: Radio Station Breaks and Programming, 1970-1972 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Nickerson, Denise: "Dark Shadows", 1969 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Nye, Russel: "Best of Everything", 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Ohlmeyer Productions: "Games People Play", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Oscard, Fifi v. Sunbrow Productions, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Packer, Anthony William: Pension and Welfare Claim, 1980-1981 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Panacea Narrowcasting: TV-Satellite Agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Parker, Woody: "Ryan's Hope", 1979 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Paul, Randolph v. AFTRA: Deposition, Jan 11, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Paul, Sidney: In the Matter of, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Peekskill Enterprises: June Taylor Dancers, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Phillip Productions: "Coliseum" Program, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Richard Astor Agency v. Brian Brownlee, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Rizzuto, Phil: Sportscaster Commercials, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - RKO General v. AFTRA: "Rambling with Gambling, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - RKO General v. AFTRA: "Rambling with Gambling, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - RKO General: WOR 60th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - RKO General/WOR: Release Agreements and Termination, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Robert J. Blum Productions: Pension and Welfare Contributions, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Roberts, Bob v. Sterling Information Services, 1972-1980 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Rosemary Brian Agency: Commission Scale Violation, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Ross, Don: Insufficient Payment (Newscaster), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Rube, Herbert Norman v. WMCA, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Saffer, Carolyn v. Harry M. Saffer, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Sahl, Mort v. Metromedia Television, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Sanchez, Cary v. Chateaubleu, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Sanchez, Raul F.: Performances for WXTV, 1980-1985 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Sanders, Bryon: "One Life to Live", 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Sax, Jay Oliver: Belly-Up LTD, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Shadow Network, 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Shafer, John: "Talk of New York" Fees, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Sheehan Telescenes: "Pippin" Exceeded Plays, May-Jun 1981 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Sheehan Telescenes Inc: "Pippin" Exceeded Plays, Jul-Nov 1981 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Sheehan Telescenes Inc: "Pippin" Exceeded Plays, 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Shelley, Joshua: "Childrens TV Workshop", 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Eugene: "The Edge of Night", 1979 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Snell, David: "One Life to Live", 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Sommers, Marc v. WABC, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Spota, George R.: "The Great Civil War", 1967 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Stone, Ernie and Sand, Les: Termination, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Stonehenge LTD: George Wallace, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Streeter, Dan: ABC 6th Day Compensation, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Stuart, Eileen: "Pleasures and Music", 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Sullivan, Ed: Assorted Claims, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Sullivan, Ed Fund: Change in Fund, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Sunrise Entertainment: "Mr. Peepers", 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Talent Agencies: A-Plus Inc. Claim, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Talent Agencies: Action Talents, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Talent Agencies: Louis Shurr Agency, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Talent Agencies: National Talent Associates Claim, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Taylor, Renee and Lord, Dick v. Carol Glaser, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Tony Awards: Bentwood Television Actor's Fee, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Trans-Atlantic Enterprises: "From the Bitter End", 1981 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Tucker, Betsey: WABC Retroactive Pay, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Tuesday Productions v. AFTRA, 1979-1981 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Bier, Linda Claim, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1981 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Hewitt, Alan Claim, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Lewis, Abby Claim, 1978-1981 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Malone, Deborah Claim, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Unemployment Insurance: McGiffert, James Claim, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Mitchell, William C. Claim, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Paglia, Regina Claim, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Young, Maureen Claim, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - United States v. Frankie Crocker, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - United States v. Comparato, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - United Talent Inc. v. AFTRA on Behalf of Marla Adams, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Velline, Robert Thomas: Artist Royalty Statement, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Vurra, Albina: "Beach Time", 1980 (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - WABC: Disc Jockeys' Public Service Announcements, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - Watson, William: Pension and Welfare Payments, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - Waggoner, Lyle and Lawrence, Vicki: Carol Burnett and Friends" Replays, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - Welfare Issues: "Billy Bogs Midday Show," "Another World," "Its Ten PM", 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - William Morris Agency: Joe Keyes Jr., Bobby Sherman, Jerry Butler, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - William Morris Agency v. Howard Cosell, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - William Morris Agency v. Ann Risley: "Saturday Night Live", 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - Williams, Robin v. George Schlatter Productions, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - Winn, David: "The Young and the Restless", 1980 (Box 49, Folder 70)
  - Wisdom, Norman: "The Ed Sullivan Show", 1967 (Box 49, Folder 71)
  - Witker, Kristi: "Sports '78", 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 72)
  - WKTU: G. Keith Alexander, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 73)
  - WKTU: David Mallow, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 74)
  - WKTU: Randy Place, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 75)
  - WKTU: Paul Robinson, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 76)
  - WNEW: "The Night and Morning Worlds of Walt Whitman", 1965 (Box 49, Folder 77)
  - WNJR: Federal Communications Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 78)
  - Wool Logo Commercials: Chico Hamilton and Jacqueline Arnold, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Yorkshire Productions, Kraft Music Hall, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Negotiations
  One of AFTRA's major functions as a union is to negotiate contracts, including aspects like wages and working conditions, for its members. The majority of the records in this series document contracts with local New York radio and television networks, with a specific emphasis on daytime drama programming and live performances taking place in the greater New York City area (such as the New York City Ballet and the New York Philharmonic). The series also includes numerous "waivers," exceptions to existing contract rules for entities interested in hiring AFTRA members.
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Jul 1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Aug-Dec 1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Jul 1971 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Aug-Dec 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Apr 1972 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, May-Dec 1972 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Mar 1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Apr-Dec 1973 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Jun 1974 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jul-Dec 1974 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Apr 1975 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, May-Dec 1975 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-May 1976 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jun-Dec 1976 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Apr 1977 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jun-Dec 1977 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Jul 1978 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Aug-Dec 1978 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, Jan-Apr 1979 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, May-Dec 1979 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers, 1985-1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Adelphi Productions, Adelphi University, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Adonis Radio Corporation, Dr. Carlton Fredericks, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Alvin Alley Dance Company, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "AMBASSADOR" Closed Circuit Broadcast, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Ballet Theatre "Don Quixote", 1984 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Forces Radio and Television Service, 1972-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Forces Radio and Television Service, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Foundation for the Blind, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Image Awards, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: American Song Festival, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Amherst Productions, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Azure Media Group, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Baby" Original Cast Recording, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Beacon Hill", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Bell, Stephen, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Benji Productions "Let's Skate America", 1981 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Bernstein's "MASS", 1972, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "The Best of Saturday Night Live", 1985 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Brentwood Television Corporation, Roy Somlyo, General Manager, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: British Broadcasting Corporation Program, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Broadway Magazine", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Burnett, Carol", 1979 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Camera Three Productions, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Cates, Joseph Company, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Cavett, Dick Show, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Charlie Bravo, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Choir School of St. Thomas Church, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Cine Centrum, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Cinema Sound Ltd., 1977-1981 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Clack Productions, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Clark, Deena Show, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Cockamamie Productions, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: CBS Records, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: CBS Records, 1976-1979 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Columbia Records "Mass in the Time of War", 1973 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Columbia Special Products "Old Time Radio", 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Columbia Special Products, "You are There", 1968-1971 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Commission on Human Rights, "Tell Pharoah", 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Compass Productions, 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Compass Productions, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Compass Productions, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Compton Advertising, Inc., 1968 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Compton Advertising, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Connecticut Public Radio, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Cosby Show", 1985-1987 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Cupid" recording by Sam Cooke, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Dance on the Railroad, The", 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Dancin'" on the Bob Hope Show, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: DCA (Dick Cox Associates) Productions, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: DCA (Dick Cox Associates) Productions, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: DIR Radio, "Haunted Lines", 1979 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Directors Group, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Dr. Ruth", 1987 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Dupont Show of the Week, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Elephant Man", 1980 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Ellen Burstyn Show" Walt Disney Pictures, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "FDR's Last Year", 1980 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "First Edition," Edwin Newman, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Four Friends", 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Garabidian, George Productions, 1974-1976 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Gleason, Jackie's "American Scene Magazine", 1979 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Gleason, Jackie's "American Scene Magazine", 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "The Great Gildersleeve," Release to Syndication, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Greengrass Enterprises, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: Hanguk Christian Broadcasting, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Hellzapoppin", 1977 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: "Hurok Attractions, Bolshoi Ballet, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Agreements and/or Waivers: ICD Pyramid, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 69)